manymoon.com 2010-03-12

# Manymoon | Privacy Agreement

We are committed to maintaining your privacy and keeping your trust, so we guarantee the following to protect your privacy:

  * We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes
  * We will never share your contact information with another user, without your consent.
  * Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with appropriate industry standard protocols and technology.

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the Manymoon service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

### Gathering Information

_Registration:_  
In order to become a Manymoon user, you must first create an account on the web site. To create an account you are required to provide your first name, last name, email address, and a password.

_Profile Information:_  
Once registered, you may provide additional information in the Profile section describing your skills and contact information. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is optional, but enables you to better identify yourself and collaborate with others. 

_Information about your Connections_  
In order to invite others to connect with you in Manymoon, you will enter their email address. This information will be used by Manymoon to send your invitation including a message that you would like to work with them. The email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation, task updates and reminders. 

All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own personally identifiable information.

_Cookies & Log Files:_  
Like most web sites, Manymoon uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows Manymoon to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.  
One type of cookie, known as a “persistent" cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your Manymoon account. The next time you visit the Manymoon web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so you will not need to log in before using the service. In order to access or change any of your private information (like title), however, you must log in again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Additionally, if you log out of the Manymoon site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Manymoon site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.   
Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Manymoon web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave Manymoon. We also receive the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Manymoon service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

_Children:_  
Children are not eligible to use our service and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

### Information Use

Manymoon is an online service dedicated to helping all types of professionals more effectively work with one another. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by Manymoon from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by Manymoon. This information can be utilized by Manymoon in such manner as Manymoon, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

_Manymoon Communications:_  
Manymoon will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. These include a series of welcome emails which help inform new users about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Manymoon related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user shares project information with you. Manymoon may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to [CustomerService@Manymoon.com](mailto:customerservice@manymoon.com).

_Customized Content:_  
Information you provide at registration or in your Profile section is also used to customize your experience on the web site. For example, when you login to your account we may display the names of users who are in the same project as you.

### Information Sharing:

_Sharing Information With Third Parties:_  
Manymoon takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. For instance, we may use a credit card processing company to bill users for subscription fees. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.  
We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by role (i.e. product managers, vice presidents), industry, geographic location, company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users’ activities on the site, please email customer service.

_Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services:_   
Manymoon may partner with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. Whenever we offer such combined services it will be your choice to make use of the combined services or not. In these cases, your personally identifiable information will only be passed from Manymoon to the partner if you choose to use the combined service.

_Communications Between Users:_   
Many emails you initiate through Manymoon, an invitation sent to a non-user for instance, will list your email address and name in the body of the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your Manymoon workspace (for example, the name of the task you created), but will never list the people to whom you’re directly connected. Other communications that you initiate through the Manymoon website, like a request for contact, will list your name in the message body but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another user if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other.

_Legal Disclaimer:_   
It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

_Accessing and Changing Your Account Information_ :   
You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your Manymoon account, at any time by logging in to your account on the Manymoon website and editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account through the Manymoon by emailing Customer Service. If you close your Manymoon account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the Manymoon Privacy Policy that you have previously agree to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the Manymoon service, please send your request to [customerservice@Manymoon.com.](mailto:customerservice@manymoon.com) Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with Manymoon under your name. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Manymoon may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

### Questions or Comments

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@Manymoon.com](mailto:privacy@manymoon.com) or contact us at:  
Manymoon  
Attn: Privacy Policy Issues  
P.O. Box 170673  
San Francisco, CA 94117
